export const data = [
    {
        question:'Jesus washed his disciples feet because',
        option1:'He was soon to be glorified',
        option2:'He wanted to serve by example',
        option3:'it was a sign of holiness',
        option4:'they needed to be washed',
        ans:2,
    },
    {
        question:'Jesus was accused of blasphemy because He said what',
        option1:'was the Messiah',
        option2:'was the Son of Man',
        option3:'would be at the right hand of power',
        option4:'would destroy the Temple and destroy it',
        ans:4,
    },
    {
        question:'The sanhedrin is',
        option1:'a Jewish temple',
        option2:'a Jewish councel of priests, scribes, elders ',
        option3:'the knesset',
        option4:'the sadducees',
        ans:2,
    },
    {
        question:'Jesus did not appeal to His Father for legions of angels to fight for Him because?',
        option1:'it was not proper for angels to fight humans',
        option2:'He could, on His own avoid the cross',
        option3:'he wanted the scriptures to be fufilled',
        option4:'the disciples were watching and praying',
        ans:3,
    },
    {
        question:'After his arrest Jesus ws taken to',
        option1:'Caiaphas',
        option2:'Pilate',
        option3:'Potiphar',
        option4:'Agrripa',
        ans:1,
    },
    {
        question:'Why did pilate send Jesus to herod during the trial',
        option1:'Jesus, as a Galilean was under Herods jurisdiction',
        option2:'Pilate has no power to pass the death sentence',
        option3:'Herods court was the last point before crucifixion',
        option4:'Herod had longed to see Jesus ',
        ans:1,
    },
    {
        question:'Herod was delighted to see Jesus because he wanted to ?',
        option1:'send Him to rome',
        option2:'sentence Him to death',
        option3:'punish Jesus for calling him a fox',
        option4:'See Him perform miracles',
        ans:4,
    },
    {
        question:'You shall be my witness in Jerusalem and in all Judea and in ........ and to the uttermost part of the earth ',
        option1:'Roms',
        option2:'Antioc',
        option3:'Damascus',
        option4:'Samaria',
        ans:4,
    },
    {
        question:'In the parable of the sower, the see which fell on the rocky ground represents those whose conversion is',
        option1:'Unfruitful',
        option2:'genuine',
        option3:'superficial',
        option4:'lasting',
        ans:3,
    },
    {
        question:'The promise of the Holy Spirit wa fufilled in?',
        option1:'Bethany',
        option2:'Bethlehem',
        option3:'carpernaum',
        option4:'Jerusalem',
        ans:4,
    },
    {
        question:'The parable of the lost sheep potrays the shepherd as being?',
        option1:'bad',
        option2:'patient',
        option3:'careless',
        option4:'loving',
        ans:4,
    },
    {
        question:'After Peter was released from prison by an angel, he went to the house of ',
        option1:'Mary, mother of Mark',
        option2:'Salome',
        option3:'Mary, Mother of James',
        option4:'Martha',
        ans:1,
    },
    {
        question:'Who was the first to be mathyred among the Apostles ',
        option1:'Peter',
        option2:'John',
        option3:'Stephen',
        option4:'Barnabas',
        ans:3,
    },
    {
        question:'Which contries has the most countries',
        option1:'Asia',
        option2:'Europe',
        option3:'North America',
        option4:'Africa',
        ans:4,
    },
    {
        question:'which of the following is needed to access the internet? ',
        option1:'Modem',
        option2:'Internet',
        option3:'Operating System',
        option4:'LAN Cable',
        ans:3,
    },
    {
        question:'A computer cannot boot if it does not have the? ',
        option1:'Application Software',
        option2:'Internet',
        option3:'Operating System',
        option4:'LAN Cable',
        ans:3,
    },
    {
        question:'I will not leave you comfortless , I will pray the Father, and he shall give another comforter that he may abide with you for ever, Who was Jesus talking to? ',
        option1:'The 12 disciples',
        option2:'The Church',
        option3:'You',
        option4:'All of the Above',
        ans:4,
    },
]